{
    "irrelevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Carrie Underwood",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Phillip Phillips.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jordin Sparks",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Phillip Phillips.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jordin Sparks",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jordin Sparks",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Phillip Phillips.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Carrie Underwood",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Phillip Phillips.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "irrelevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Phillip Phillips.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Phillip Phillips.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Kris Allen",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Phillip Phillips.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Candice Glover.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Canaan James Hill",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Caleb Johnson.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Canaan James Hill",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Canaan James Hill.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Canaan James Hill",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was...",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Caleb Johnson.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Victor Solomon.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Thunderstorm Artis.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Caleb Kennedy.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Candice Glover.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Caleb Johnson.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Caleb Johnson.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Caleb Kennedy.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Carrie Underwood",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Candice Glover.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Caleb Johnson.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Ch\u00e9",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Canaan James Hill",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Caleb Johnson.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Canaan James Hill",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Canaan James Hill.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Canaan James Hill",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Kolbi Jordan",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Caleb Johnson.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Kolbi Jordan",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Kolbi Jordan.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Candice Glover.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Kolbi Jordan.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Canaan James Hill.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Canaan James Hill.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Canaan James Hill.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Candice Glover.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Canaan James Hill.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Thunderstorm Artis.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Canaan James Hill.",
            "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ]
}